This program will accept one or two command line arguments. The first argument is the name of a battleship puzzle board. This sample file begins with the dimensions of the board. Next, we give the number of cells in each row and each column that are occupied by a ship. The other cells in the row are open water. Then, we have a simple list of the ships that must be placed on that board. All ships are 1 cell wide, but each ship type has a different length (# of cells): submarine = 1, destroyer = 2, cruiser = 3, battleship = 4, carrier = 5, cargo = 6, and tanker = 7. 

The task is to place the ships on the board satisfying the counts for each row. One important rule in placing the ships is that no two ships may occupy adjacent cells (including the diagonal). 

If the optional second argument find_all_solutions is not specified, the program will output any single valid solution to the puzzle. If the optional argument find_all_solutions is specified, the program will output all valid, unique solutions (in any order) and then also print at the bottom the number of solutions found. If the puzzle has no solutions, the program will print "No solutions".